// Questions array which is exported to script.js
export const myQuestions = [{
    question: "What year did WW1 start?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "1912",
        answer2: "1914",
        answer3: "1918",
        answer4: "1939"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer2"
},
{
    question: "Who was the British Prime Minister during the Falklands War?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "John Major",
        answer2: "Tony Blair",
        answer3: "Margaret Thatcher",
        answer4: "Harold Wilson"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer3"
},
{
    question: "What year was the Cuban Missile Crisis?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "1952",
        answer2: "1962",
        answer3: "1964",
        answer4: "1948"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer2"
},
{
    question: "Who was the Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Boer War?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "Lord Churchill",
        answer2: "Lord Salisbury",
        answer3: "Lord Aberdeen",
        answer4: "Lord Gladstone"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer2"
},
{
    question: "What year did the Battle of the Somme take place?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "1942",
        answer2: "1916",
        answer3: "1917",
        answer4: "1940"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer2"
},
{
    question: "Which of the below was not part of the Russian Civil War 1917-1923?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "Red Army",
        answer2: "Blue Army",
        answer3: "Green Army",
        answer4: "White Army"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer2"
},
{
    question: "What is the name of the peacekeeping organisation formed after WWII?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "United Nations",
        answer2: "NATO",
        answer3: "Warsaw Pact",
        answer4: "Partnership for Peace"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer1"
},
{
    question: "The Tuskegee Airmen constituted a U.S. Army unit drawn from which group?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "African Americans",
        answer2: "Women",
        answer3: "WW1 Veterans",
        answer4: "Youths under age 18"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer1"
},
{
    question: "When was the Korean Armistice Agreement signed?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "1951",
        answer2: "1950",
        answer3: "1952",
        answer4: "1953"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer4"
},
{
    question: "How long did the Bosnian War last?",
    answers: {
        answer1: "3 years",
        answer2: "4 years",
        answer3: "5 years",
        answer4: "2 years"
    },
    correctAnswer: "answer1"
}
];
